fate-go.us 2017-10-23

# Privacy Policy｜Fate/Grand Order Official USA Website

## Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy describes our policies on the collection, use and disclosure of your information in connection with your use of our websites, emails, and mobile applications (“Site” or “Sites”). Aniplex of America Inc. (“AOA”) is a wholly owned subsidiary of Aniplex Inc. Information collected on this Site may be used in the manner described below by AOA, Aniplex Inc., agents, subsidiaries, trusted partners and affiliates acting on our behalf (collectively, “Aniplex”). When used herein, the terms “we”, “us” and “our” refer to Aniplex.

When this Privacy Policy uses the term “personal information,” we mean information that identifies a particular individual, such as full name, street address, telephone number or email address.

We encourage you to review the entire Privacy Policy, which consists of the sections listed below.

  * Collection and Use of Personal Information
  * Transactions
  * Information Sharing
  * Tracking Technologies
  * Security
  * Updating Your Personal Information
  * Consent to Processing
  * Additional Information
  * Changes to This Policy
  * Your California Privacy Rights
  * Questions About This Privacy Policy

### Collection and Use of Personal Information

We may collect the following personal information from you:  
# Contact information such as email address;  
# Unique identifiers such as date of birth, user name, account ID;  
# Preference and other information such as favorite character(s); and  
# Information as to your computer or mobile device which you use the Sites, such as the domain name, Internet Service Provider, browser type and version, mobile device ID, operating system and device type, average time spent on our Site(s), pages viewed, information accessed, the Internet Protocol (IP) address you use to connect to the Internet and related geographical information

### Transactions

You may purchase certain items from some of our Site(s). This Privacy Policy applies to any personal information you provide in connection with any such purchases. Insome instances, you may be directed to a third party site to initiate your transaction. These third party sites will be clearly identified and link to their own privacy policies so you know which company is collecting your personal information. You should refer to those policies for any privacy-related concerns regarding your purchase with them.

### Information Sharing

We will share your personal information with third parties in the ways that are described in this Privacy Policy. We may provide your personal information to companies that help us with our business activities (e.g. assisting us in Site operations, providing customer service, etc.) or that assist us in improving our products, content, services or advertising. These companies are authorized to use your personal information only as necessary to provide these services.

We may also share your personal information:  
# As required by law, such as to comply with a subpoena or similar legal process  
# When we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud or respond to a government request  
# In connection with a corporate change including a merger, acquisition or sale of assets  
# To any other third party with your prior consent to do so 

### Tracking Technologies

We and our third party partners may automatically collect information as you browse our Site(s) such as the domain name, Internet Service Provider, browser type and version, mobile device ID, operating system and device type, average time spent on our Site(s), pages viewed, information accessed, the Internet Protocol (IP) address you use to connect to the Internet and related geographical information about your computer or mobile device. Such information is sometimes referred to as web analytics and/or clickstream data.

We and our third party partners use cookies and other technologies such as web beacons to keep track of your visits, preferences and profile information. This information is used to make our Site(s) easier to use, improve our advertising, and to provide you with a more personal and convenient experience. For example, we may use this information to store some of your preferences or to provide you with tailored advertisements related to your specific interests. Additionally, should you choose to enroll, we and our third party partners may use this information to allow you to participate in one of our fan rewards programs. To learn more about the use of cookies in online advertising, including how to manage or delete them, please visit the following website:  
[www.networkadvertising.org/understanding-online-advertising/](http://www.networkadvertising.org/understanding-online-advertising/).

We and some of our third party partners use Flash cookies to store some of your preferences or personal information. For more information on Flash cookies and how to manage privacy and storage settings, please visit the following website:  
<http://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager.html>

In some of our email messages, we use “click-through URLs” or pixel tags to determine whether the email has been opened and to measure the effectiveness of our customer communications. This data may also be used to gauge your interest in particular topics, so we can deliver a more relevant, personal and convenient user-experience. 

### Security

We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and after receipt. However, no method of transmission over the Internet or method of electronic storage is 100% secure and we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

### Updating Your Personal Information

If you wish to review and update your personal information, cancel your account or request that we no longer use your information to provide you services, please send email to the address below.  
Support@fate-go.us 

### Consent to Processing

Our Sites are operated in the United States, Canada and Japan. If you are located in the European Union or elsewhere outside of the United States, Canada and Japan, please be aware that information we collect will be transferred to and processed in the United States, Canada or Japan. By using our Sites, or providing us with any information, you fully understand and unambiguously consent to this transfer, processing and storage of your information in the United States, Canada and Japan, jurisdictions in which the privacy laws may not be as comprehensive as those in the country where you reside and/or are a citizen.

### Additional Information

If you feel that we have unknowingly collected information from someone under the age of 13, please contact us immediately and this information will be removed.

For more information on how to protect your children online:

Visit www.OnGuardOnline.gov for social networking safety tips for parents and youth.

### Changes To This Policy

By using our Site(s), you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy. We may amend this Privacy Policy at any time and, as such, we encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices. If we make a material change to the way in which we collect, use, and/or share your personal information, we will send an email to users who have provided an email address or post a notice on our Site(s) prior to the change becoming effective. Your continued use of the Site(s) after a revised version of this Privacy Policy has been posted will signify your consent to the terms of such revised policy.

### Your California Privacy Rights

If you are a California resident, California Civil Code Section 1798.83 provides you the right to receive (a) information identifying any third party(ies) to whom we may have disclosed, within the preceding calendar year, your personal information for that third party’s direct marketing purposes; and (b) a description of the categories of personal information disclosed. To obtain such information free of charge, please write or email to us at the address below. We will respond to these requests within thirty (30) days. Requests that come to us by other means may result in a delayed response.

### Questions About This Privacy Policy

If you have questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy, you should first contact AOA. You can contact us about this Privacy Policy by writing us:

Aniplex of America Inc.  
2120 Colorado Ave. #220 Santa Monica CA 90404 U.S.A.  
Email: support@fate-go.us

Or you can click [here](mailto:support@fate-go.us) to submit feedback online.
